Hi!
Most people know the trick for finding 11 multiplied by a single digit.
For example, 11x7=77.
It gets a little more difficult when we want to multiply 11 by 2 digit numbers.
Let's take 11x25 as our example.
The first step is to take 25 and separate the 2 and 5 into two separate numbers.
Then we want to add 2 and 5 together to equal 7.
7 goes right between the 2 and the 5.
275 is the answer.
We got this by adding the 2 numbers together and thee sticking the answer in the middle.
Let's try a little bit harder now.
11x69.
We know that 6+9=15, but 15 is a little too big to go in the middle.
What we do is we keep the 5 in the middle and carry the 1 over to the first number, which makes it 7.
Now we have 759.
Whenever you're doing math in your head, the most important part is being able to visualize the numbers.
The more you practice, the better you're going to get.